just just
welcome to speed welcome to our country deep in our search
where are you hear about his real estate Christmas
banking crisis Jess crisis
ruled downgrading 0 risk premiums
speculation against me 25 percent unemployment
veiled on a good week who run in front of bulls for fun heard about to complete
feel sorry for ourselves because what we see
you know be is the glass half empty or half full with
is a country full of opportunity in the midst of the crisis
we've already had some great news every mention River Brewing European football
champions
the but seriously it's not all about sex the Spanish tourism sector
is an all-time high in 2011
tourism revenue grew by 14 percent and we're the country with the second
highest tourism revenue in the world second
only to the United States last year we had fifty seven million foreign visitors
spain has a population 46 min and that figure will be even higher in 2012
our exports of goods and services grew by
18 percent between 2009 and 2011
and we reduced our trade deficit balance significantly
we also reinforced our efforts to globalize our company's
do you know who is leading the Panama Canal expansion
who is going to construct the first high-speed train in the Middle East
between Mecca and Medina a consortium a Spanish bonds
or
who manages airports in cities such as London Orlando and all the time
who is going to construct offshore wind farms in Scotland of
who supplies wind turbines to the world's leading economies
of who is building Dessau nation plantain
Adelaide and the Atacama Desert who systems were used to manage most if your
flight bookings to come
I'll now I'm through Germany put in charge of their
air traffic control system saving time and fuel who is developing a vaccine for
Alzheimer's disease
year or who supplied the weather station for the curiosity Mars rover
I'm doom
I
the sorry yeah we did that too
that's right Spanish companies are doing
own these things and more led by qualified creatives sustainability
conscious professionals
just ironically in the midst to the banking crisis
and according to your own money we have the best bank in the world
and another one that isn't too far behind summits
even call the industry has been shaken to its foundations
of we have an innovative global telecommunications company
able to provide service to over 300 million customers
in 25 countries our company's
are at the forefront of growth sectors such as cleantech
and 13 percent of our energy consumption comes from renewables
we are the world's leading country installed solar energy
and the fourth largest in wind energy we also have giant serve the global fashion
industry
and multiple companies in this industry able to dress
and supply footwear for the planet this is a country
which today in these turbulent times is incubating a growing number of new
dynamic companies ready to make the leap and take their place in the world
rankings
the economic crisis is harnessing the entrepreneurial spirit
endeavor and creativity I'm spaniards no matter what anybody says
we worked as hard as we party okay guys
they see speed is a fantastic country to live it perhaps it's because mr.
sunshine
our guest room worked for six or perhaps because of our health care system
proved wrong speed has the third highest life expectancy in the world
according to the OCD we can raise that to number two if you're lucky enough to
be female
yeah I think we can also say that we have a big heart
wealth that's actually been proven spain has the highest
organ donation rate in the world and last year the number of transplants
increased by 20 percent yet another reason to be optimistic
welcome to speed we hope you enjoy your stay